<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weather</string>
    <string name="home">Search</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="on_boarding_title">Weather Whisper</string>
    <string name="on_boarding_subtitle">Hear the Secrets of the Skies</string>
    <string name="lets_get_started">Let\'s go</string>
    <string name="celcius_symbol">℃</string>
    <string name="farenheit_symbol">℉</string>
    <string name="feels_like">Feels like</string>
    <string name="more">More</string>
    <string name="visibility">visibility</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="degree_symbol">°</string>
    <string name="temp_unit">Temperature unit</string>
    <string name="temp">Temperature</string>
    <string name="city">City</string>
    <string name="celcius">Celsius(℃)</string>
    <string name="farenheit">Fahrenheit(℉)</string>
    <string name="enter_valid_city_name">Please enter a valid city name</string>
    <string name="ms">meter / sec</string>
    <string name="mh">miles / hour</string>
    <string name="city_desc">Add the city name that you want to save in the home screen</string>
    <string name="search_desc">Find the city name that you want to know the detailed weather info at this time.</string>
    <string name="save">save</string>
    <string name="save_city">Saved cities</string>
    <string name="current_air_quality">Current air quality</string>
    <string name="current_air_pollut">Current air Pollutants</string>
    <string name="current_clouds">Current cloudiness</string>
    <string name="aqi">AQI</string>
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="fair">Fair</string>
    <string name="moderate">Moderate</string>
    <string name="poor">Poor</string>
    <string name="very_poor">Very poor</string>
    <string name="aqi_desc">Think of the AQI as a yardstick that runs from 1 to 5. For example , an AQI value of 1 represents good air quality, while an AQI value over 4 represents  hazardous air quality. </string>
    <string name="o3">O3</string>
    <string name="pm25">PM25</string>
    <string name="pm10">PM10</string>
    <string name="no2">NO2</string>
    <string name="microgram">μg/m3</string>
    <string name="km">km</string>
    <string name="error_msg">Something went wrong, please make sure that you are connected and that you have entered a valid city name.</string>
    <string name="no2desc">Nitrogen dioxide is a reddish-brown gas formed from the burning of fossil fuels, primarily in vehicles and power plants. It is a prominent component of air pollution in urban areas. High concentrations of NO2 can contribute to respiratory problems and worsen existing respiratory conditions. It also plays a role in the formation of other air pollutants, such as ozone and particulate matter.</string>
    <string name="pm10desc">PM10 refers to slightly larger particles with a diameter of 10 micrometers or smaller. These particles can come from similar sources as PM2.5, including vehicle emissions, industrial activities, and dust storms. While larger than PM2.5, PM10 particles can still enter the respiratory system and cause health issues, particularly for individuals with respiratory conditions.</string>
    <string name="pm25desc">PM2.5 refers to fine particles suspended in the air with a diameter of 2.5 micrometers or smaller. These particles can be emitted directly from sources such as vehicle exhaust, industrial processes, and wildfires, or they can form from the chemical reactions of pollutants in the atmosphere. PM2.5 can penetrate deep into the respiratory system and may cause or worsen respiratory and cardiovascular problems.</string>
    <string name="o3desc">Ozone is a gas composed of three oxygen molecules. It is a major component of smog and is primarily formed from pollutants emitted by vehicles, industrial processes, and chemical solvents. Ozone in the lower atmosphere is considered a pollutant and can cause respiratory issues, especially for individuals with asthma or other respiratory conditions.</string>
</resources>